

CONTACT ME AT

- Currently ValenciaSpain
- vgilabert.94@gmail.com
- https://github.com/vgilabert94
- in <u>@vgilabert</u>

SKILLS SUMMARY

- ••• Python
- •••• MATLAB
- •••• Machine Learning
- Image Processing (Computer vision)
- •••• Labview
- ••• C / C++

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

- Data Science Bootcamp using Python. (Udemy)
- Machine Learning
 Stanford University (Coursera)
- Intermediate Python for Data
 Science
 Datacamp
- Introduction of Deep Learning University of Alicante

VICENTE GILABERT MAÑO

TELECOMMUNICATIONS ENGINEER
COMPUTER VISION ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a telecommunications engineer specialised in artificial intelligence and computer vision. I am ready to continue learning and training to learn the most advanced technologies/algorithms. I am responsible in my tasks and able to learn constantly, trying to achieve the best results by teamwork, providing new ideas and solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Computer Vision Research Engineer SEDDI | Sep 2022 - Now

- Research and development of computer vision algorithms to bring new functionalities and technologies to Textura.ai.
- Review the state of the art in various areas of computer vision.
 Image retrieval, image quality assessment, image restoration (enhancement), etc.
- Python, pytorch, lightning, opencv, sk-image, PIL, numpy, scipy, pandas, matplotlib, ONNX, kornia, streamlit, etc.

Junior Computer Vision Engineer

- AUTIS Ingenieros S.L. | Oct 2019 Sep 2021
- Review, maintenance and improvement of the operation of computer vision systems in projects already in production.
- Commissioning of international computer vision projects in industry. I traveled abroad for FORD, TOYOTA, NISSSAN, TESLA.
- LabVIEW programming of imagen processing tools.

Research Internship University of Alicante | Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

- Machine Learning and Neural Networks especially CNN
- Image Processing
- Image Labeling to create an OMR dataset to train a ML model.
- Tools:
 - Python + Tensorflow + Keras + OpenCV + Numpy
 - o Matlab

Computer Technician

Ajuntament d'Oliva (Oliva) | Jul 2014 - Sep 2014

Web Developer. Internship

Quasar formacion (Gandia) | Mar 2014 - Jun 2014

Computer Technician. Internship

Centre Informàtic Oliva (Oliva) | Mar 2012 - Jun 2012



CONTACT ME AT

- Currently ValenciaSpain
- vgilabert.94@gmail.com
- https://github.com/vgilabert94
- in <u>@vgilabert</u>

SKILLS SUMMARY

- ••• Python
- •••• MATLAB
- •••• Machine Learning
- Image Processing (Computer vision)
- •••• Labview
- • • Deep Learning

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

- Data Science Bootcamp using Python. (Udemy)
- Machine Learning
 Stanford University (Coursera)
- Intermediate Python for Data
 Science
 Datacamp
- Introduction of Deep Learning University of Alicante

VICENTE GILABERT MAÑO

TELECOMMUNICATIONS ENGINEER
COMPUTER VISION ENGINEER

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Rey Juan Carlos University

Master degree in Computer Vision | Sep 2021 - Jun 2022

- Image and video processing, machine and deep learning, biometrics, robotics, 3D vision, medical image.
- Python, OpenCV, SciPy, Keras (TF), MATLAB.
- Master thesis: Detection of minimum repeatable tile in fabric textures using CNN activations.

Exchange. Federico Santa Maria Technical University. Valparaíso (Chile)

Degree in Sound and Image Engineering in Telecommunications. | Feb 2019 - Jul 2019

• Subjects studied: Computer Project Management, Antennas and Propagation, Wireless Networks and Computer Vision

University Of Alicante

Degree in Sound and Image Engineering in Telecommunications. | 2014 - 2019

• Thesis involved studying the Segmentation of handwritten music documents using Machine Learning.

IES Maria Enriquez (Gandia)

Senior Technician in Administration of Networked Computer Systems. | 2012 - 2014

IES Enric Valor

Technician in Microcomputer Systems and Networking | 2010 - 2012

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native
- Valencian/Catalan: Native
- English: B1 Certificate (ACLES 2017).
 - English course in Dublin for two months. (2017)
 - Four months working in the US. (2020-2021)